are you looking for a term insurance
plan
which financially protects your wife and
children
introducing icici pro i protect smart
and its seven benefits that you must
know
[Music]
first i protect smart premium
comfortably fits into your budget
even after paying off all your monthly
bills
just what your wallet asked for
second the sooner you buy term plan
online
the better off you will be premiums will
be lower
and cover will be longer till the age of
75.
third i protect smart gives you option
for full claim payout
on the first diagnosis of any of 34
critical illnesses
no hospital bills required that's
correct
no bills just a photocopy of your
diagnosis report will do
moreover this option covers you for 30
years
without any change in premium
fourth i protect smart gives your
nominees four ways to receive
insurance money first
lump sum second regular monthly income
[Music]
third increasing monthly income
and the newly launched lump sum plus
regular monthly income
thus all the important needs of your
children and wife
are met on time
fifth i protect smart in all its plan
options
helps you put up a big fight against
major terminal illnesses
including aids by paying the insurance
money before death
[Music]
sixth you may add the accidental death
benefit in i protect smart
during or after the purchase of the
policy with the maximum cover
up to rupees 2 crores
7. i protect smart gives you the option
to buy the policy online
under mwp act the married women property
act
helps provide protection against
wrongful claims
so that the insurance amount goes to no
one else
but only to your wife and children
go get the seven fold protection online
[Music]
today
you